<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Oliver!]]></title>
  <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-08T17:55:49-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://oliverdamien.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Melissa & Rebecca]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skinny Boy!]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/11/06/skinny-boy/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/11/06/skinny-boy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver had his four-month pediatrician appointment yesterday! The doctor said he looks great &mdash; except that he is a little skinny. He dropped from the 25th percentile for weight at two months to the 5th percentile for weight at four months. We talked about various strategies for helping him gain weight &mdash; giving him an ounce more at each feeding, feeding him a 50/50 ratio of breast milk to formula (instead of 60/40 like we had been doing), and even introducing solids a little early. We&rsquo;ve already gotten started on these things, and hope that little Oliver bulks up a bit by his six-month well visit. His height is at the 45th percentile and his head circumference is at the 35th percentile, both of which are just fine based on where he&rsquo;s been in the past.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oliver Starts Child Care]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/11/06/oliver-starts-child-care/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/11/06/oliver-starts-child-care</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m getting ready to head back to work, so Oliver is slowly transitioning into child care. We found a really great child care center that&rsquo;s very close to my work, so I can drop him off on my way to work, pick him up on my way home from work, and even visit in the middle of the day if I want to.</p>

<p>Oliver and I toured the whole center a while back, and then we visited both infant rooms together with Rebecca, and then he and I visited his infant room and spent some time with his primary child care provider. Tomorrow, Oliver will go to child care all on his own in the morning, from around 9:30 to around 1:30, so he can start getting used to being there without me. We&rsquo;ll do the same thing the following Tuesday, and then he&rsquo;ll go full days on Tuesday and Wednesday the following week when I start back to work. The next week (Thanksgiving week), he&rsquo;ll go full days on Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday, which will be his regular child care schedule.</p>

<p>I really hope tomorrow goes well! I&rsquo;m most worried about him learning to sleep at child care. At home, he&rsquo;s still in his rock-n-play sleeper (an inclined rocking bassinet). At child care, he&rsquo;ll be in a crib. At home, he wears a sleep sack and a swaddle strap for naps and nights, to keep his arms from flailing. At child care, he&rsquo;ll just be in a sleep sack. I&rsquo;m glad that his room has a separate alcove where all the cribs are, and the lights are turned low in that part of the room, and they have a sound machine going all the time. I hope those things make it a bit easier for him to learn how to sleep there.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just Oliver and Mommy]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/16/just-oliver-and-mommy/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/16/just-oliver-and-mommy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Rebecca had to travel to her corporate headquarters recently &mdash; for nine days &mdash; so it was just Oliver and Mommy that whole time. In addition to our typical daytime activities, I planned lots of lunches and dinners with friends, so we&rsquo;d stay busy while Rebecca was away. All of that planning paid off &mdash; our week together went great!</p>

<p>Oliver was a great sleeper while Rebecca was away. Well, he&rsquo;s always a great sleeper, and thankfully that continued while she was away. The first morning we were on our own together, he woke up in the morning, ate, and then went back to sleep for three hours. While he slept, I was able to do all kinds of things, including showering and eating breakfast. I just about ran out of things to do before he finally woke up.</p>

<p>The shortest overnight sleeping stretch Oliver had the whole time Rebecca was away was 7 hours. And usually he slept from sometime between 9:30 and 11:00 at night until between 7:00 and 7:45 the next morning.</p>

<p>Rebecca really missed Oliver while she was away, so I took cute pictures of him and texted them to her. She really liked that. We also did a google hangout one night. I put Oliver on his play mat and suspended the iPad above him where I usually have a mirror suspended. I accidentally dropped the iPad on him at one point, but it could have been worse. He was definitely surprised and upset, but he recovered quickly.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tall Boy]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/05/tall-boy/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/05/tall-boy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We saw the pediatrician again today, and Oliver grew two whole inches in just one month! He&rsquo;s now 23-&frac12; inches long. That means he&rsquo;s at the 60th percentile for height (he was at the 25th percentile last month). His weight is holding steady at the 25th percentile (10 pounds 14 ounces at this visit). His head circumference increased just a little bit, to the 30th percentile (from the 25th percentile at the last visit). So he&rsquo;s a tall, lean baby boy!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleeping Like a Baby]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/04/sleeping-like-a-baby/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/04/sleeping-like-a-baby</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver sleeps through the night! Not always, but a lot of the time. For a week straight recently, he slept at least seven consecutive hours. We kind of can&rsquo;t believe it, and we don&rsquo;t really expect it to last. But wouldn&rsquo;t it be nice if it did?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smiley Oliver]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/03/smiley-oliver/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/03/smiley-oliver</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver has gotten super-smiley these days. He makes great eye contact when he&rsquo;s smiling at you, and he&rsquo;s just so engaging. We don&rsquo;t have many pics of his new level of smiley-ness yet, but here are a few.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9658603340/" title="IMG_5808 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm6.staticflickr.com/5521/9658603340_5c70bfac3c.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5808"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9655373839/" title="IMG_5818 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7308/9655373839_cf94f58b2b.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5818"></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labor Day Weekend Family Fun!]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/02/labor-day-weekend-family-fun/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/09/02/labor-day-weekend-family-fun</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On Labor Day weekend, Oliver&rsquo;s Aunt Morgan, Uncle Albert, and Uncle Garrett all came for a visit. Oliver had a great time with all of them. Aunt Morgan put him to sleep a few times, Uncle Albert giggled at him, and Uncle Garrett entertained him by crinkling parchment paper.</p>

<p>On Sunday, the crew all went to A Southern Season, a board game store, and the Asian market. I wanted to take a shower, and if I had gone we would have needed to take two cars. So I stayed behind and got things done around the house, ran some errands, and showered. I was without my baby for nearly three hours, and I was so glad to see him again when he returned! Rebecca said he was a total angel the entire time.</p>

<p>Here are some pics of Oliver hanging out with his aunt and uncles:</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9638777510/" title="IMG_5608 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3778/9638777510_3193ab4295.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5608"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9638811330/" title="IMG_5689 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2889/9638811330_8522ca7301.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5689"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9635581273/" title="IMG_5736 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3714/9635581273_7db1e7e576.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5736"></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oliver's New York Grandparents Visit]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/29/NY-grandparents-visit/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/29/NY-grandparents-visit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver&rsquo;s New York grandparents &mdash; Rebecca&rsquo;s parents &mdash; came for a week-long visit a few weeks ago. Oliver got lots of love and cuddles from his grandma and grandpa. We all spent time on the porch together (under the FANS &mdash; one of Oliver&rsquo;s favorite things in the whole world!). They also took Oliver on some walks around the neighborhood.</p>

<p>We all went out to Elmo&rsquo;s for breakfast one day, to Monuts for breakfast another day, and to Nana Taco for lunch another day. Oliver&rsquo;s grandma took Rebecca&rsquo;s place at a baby massage class one afternoon; unfortunately, Oliver slept through most of it and then woke up hungry, so we practiced on the plastic baby mannequins instead of on Oliver.</p>

<p>Oliver also got to spend time with his grandma and grandpa when they babysat him for a few hours one morning while we checked out child care options for when I return to work in November. They also babysat Oliver one evening so Rebecca and I could go out for a nice dinner. They said he was a very sweet boy both times.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9585920252/" title="IMG_5379 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7351/9585920252_d3253d412d.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5379"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9583129639/" title="IMG_5368 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm6.staticflickr.com/5515/9583129639_4d22e07312.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5368"></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oliver Likes His Legs]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/20/oliver-likes-his-legs/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/20/oliver-likes-his-legs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver&rsquo;s latest past-time is to &ldquo;stand&rdquo; on my lap with support. His legs feel sooo strong when he does this. His whole body tenses up with the effort of it. He bobs his head up and down, makes whatever his latest favorite noise is, and moves his little arms all around. It&rsquo;s totally cute. Whenever he&rsquo;s even a little bit fussy, I just stand him on my lap and start telling him what a strong boy he is. He stops fussing right away and gets all focused on using those little legs of his.</p>

<p>We&rsquo;ll get some pictures soon and post them here.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Boy Can Roll Over]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/12/our-boy-can-roll-over/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/12/our-boy-can-roll-over</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yep, it&rsquo;s true. Our boy can roll over, front to back. It&rsquo;s pretty amazing. Last night we had some friends over for dinner, and I decided to put him down on the floor for tummy time after I changed his diaper. I put him face down on the floor, with his arms bent underneath him like I normally do. He lifted his head waaay up, so he was looking straight at me where I was positioned in front of him on the floor. And then it happened. He pushed off with his right arm and wound up halfway between his side and his back (don&rsquo;t ask me how he stalled out at precisely that position). After I praised him a ton, I yelled to Rebecca and our guests, &ldquo;You guys have got to come in here!&rdquo; They came and I told them what Oliver had done. I didn&rsquo;t put him back on his tummy for some reason; I&rsquo;m not sure why. I think I was afraid it was a fluke and he wouldn&rsquo;t do it again.</p>

<p>Then this morning after a diaper change, I put him down for tummy time again. It was the same thing, only faster. He lifted his head waaay up, pushed off with his right arm, and he was on his back. I praised him a ton and put him back on his tummy. He did it again. Pretty amazing.</p>

<p>Then this afternoon after a diaper change, I decided to put him down again. He did the whole thing again, except pushed off with his left arm this time. I called Rebecca in so she could witness the awesomeness of our boy. He did it again, pushing off with his left arm again. She was impressed.</p>

<p>Next time I hope to get a video of it. But Rebecca says that maybe four times rolling over in one day is enough, so it likely will be tomorrow before I can videotape him. Bummer. I think I&rsquo;m even more excited about this than Oliver.</p>

<p>Update: here&rsquo;s a video!</p>

<iframe src="http://oliverdamien.com//player.vimeo.com/video/73529626" width="500" height="889" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p> <p><a href="http://vimeo.com/73529626">Oliver rolling over</a> from <a href="http://vimeo.com/rmurphey">Rebecca Murphey</a> on <a href="https://vimeo.com">Vimeo</a>.</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Pediatrician Visit]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/08/another-pediatrician-visit/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/08/another-pediatrician-visit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver had another pediatrician visit today. He is 9 pounds 8 ounces and 21-&frac12; inches long. He is at the 25th percentile for height, for weight, and for head circumference. His pediatrician said he was &ldquo;perfectly in proportion to himself.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He also had to get his second Hepatitis B shot today. He did not like it one bit, but he calmed quickly once I picked him up and held him close.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oliver Loves Bath Time]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/06/oliver-loves-bath-time/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/06/oliver-loves-bath-time</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver had another bath today, and he is really starting to like them!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9452435311/" title="IMG_5131 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7289/9452435311_d295e7ff29.jpg" width="333" height="500" alt="IMG_5131"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9452440141/" title="IMG_5135 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm6.staticflickr.com/5443/9452440141_1065c9f3a3.jpg" width="333" height="500" alt="IMG_5135"></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oliver's Florida Grandparents Visit]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/02/FL-grandparents-visit/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/08/02/FL-grandparents-visit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week, my parents &mdash; Oliver&rsquo;s Florida grandparents &mdash; came for a visit. Oliver had a nice time getting lots of attention from them. He got a horsey ride and napped with Grandpa, and went on walks and cuddled with Grandma.</p>

<p>The timing of my parents&#8217; visit was especially good because Rebecca got sick on Tuesday and couldn&rsquo;t help me with Oliver much overnight for several nights. So I was very happy to see my Mom and Dad each morning!</p>

<p>My parents and I took Oliver on quite a few outings this week. We went to Babies R Us, Buy Buy Baby, Duke Gardens, Elmo&rsquo;s, A Southern Season, and Locopops, and Dad went to Pelican&rsquo;s Snoballs to get us some shaved ice. The weather was mostly nice this week, so we also went on a lot of neighborhood walks.</p>

<p>My parents also babysat Oliver on Friday night so Rebecca and I could go out to dinner. We got some quick burgers at Bull City Burger. It was nice for the two of us to have some time together &mdash; but we were definitely ready to get home to see Oliver too.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9452429341/" title="IMG_5055 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3746/9452429341_28a5e247bc.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_5055"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9455212198/" title="IMG_5075 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm6.staticflickr.com/5532/9455212198_bd1836d95e.jpg" width="333" height="500" alt="IMG_5075"></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oliver's First Real Pediatrician Visit]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/16/first-pediatrician-visit/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/16/first-pediatrician-visit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Oliver had his first real pediatrician visit today! He was seen by the doctors in the hospital where he was born when he was just a few days old, but this was his first appointment with his actual pediatrician in North Carolina.</p>

<p>The pediatrician checked Oliver out, and said he seemed very healthy. She recommended that we do a newborn screening, because she predicted that it would be difficult to get the results of the newborn screening done in the hospital where Oliver was born. We said that was fine, so poor Oliver had to have his heel stuck and then a series of circles on a piece of paper filled in with his blood. Needless to say, he did not like that at all.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Long Trip Home]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/12/long-trip-home/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/12/long-trip-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today was a big day &mdash; the day we got to fly home to North Carolina with Oliver. Although we really looked forward to being home, we were worried that it would be a hard trip for Oliver. He&rsquo;d be in unfamiliar surroundings, and taking off and landing might be uncomfortable for him. We needn&rsquo;t have worried. He did great. He slept most of the time (including during takeoff and landing). He was so sleepy that we had to wake him for most of his feedings. I couldn&rsquo;t get him to nurse very much at all, which was a little concerning, but I figured I&rsquo;d work with him on that when we got to North Carolina.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, there&rsquo;s no direct flight from Denver to Raleigh-Durham, so we needed to book our flight through Atlanta. Let&rsquo;s just say that Atlanta is not Rebecca&rsquo;s favorite airport. It is usually very crowded and busy, with insufficient seating at the gates. To make matters worse, our flight out of Atlanta was delayed by about an hour and a half. It turns out, though, that traveling with a newborn is a good conversation-starter. We were very popular people at our gate. Lots of people wanted to hear our story (and give us their opinions on various child-rearing tactics). We were impressed that no one tried to touch Oliver or asked to hold him.</p>

<p>The flight crew on the flight from Atlanta to Raleigh-Durham were very nice, and gave us &ldquo;wings&rdquo; (one for each of us and one for Oliver). They also gave us a bottle of wine to congratulate us on adopting Oliver.</p>

<p>We arrived around midnight, and our friend Julie picked us up in our car (so the carseat was all set). We crammed all the luggage into the car, and headed home. We tried to get to bed as quickly as possible, but we had to do a little unpacking to be sure we had all the baby gear we&rsquo;d need for the night. We finally got to bed a little after 2:00 am. We were exhausted after our long day.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Carolina Says We Can Come Home!]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/11/nc-icpc/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-11T23:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/11/nc-icpc</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today we learned that we got clearance from North Carolina to enter the state with Oliver! Rebecca immediately got online and booked plane tickets home for us tomorrow. The court hearing for the relinquishment of the birth parents&#8217; rights is not until early next week, so we will be leaving the state &ldquo;at risk&rdquo; &mdash; if anything goes awry with rights relinquishment, we&rsquo;ll need to return to Colorado with Oliver. But we think the chances of that are low, and we really want to be home with him as soon as possible.</p>

<p>We also got together with Oliver&rsquo;s birth mom and her mom tonight. We ate dinner together, exchanged contact information, admired how great Oliver&rsquo;s birth mom looks so soon after Oliver&rsquo;s birth, and talked about how wonderful Oliver is. It was nice to spend that time together.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Day Oliver's Cord Fell Off]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/11/umbilical-cord/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-11T08:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/11/umbilical-cord</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last night when we were getting Oliver ready for bed, we noticed that his umbilical cord was barely still attached. So I wasn&rsquo;t surprised when Rebecca changed Oliver this morning and noticed that it had fallen off. I immediately tore apart the bed looking for it. I found it, and now it&rsquo;s saved with Oliver&rsquo;s other keepsakes (like his hospital ID bands).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado Says We Can Leave!]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/10/co-icpc/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/10/co-icpc</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today was the day we learned that we got clearance from Colorado to leave the state with Oliver. We were so happy! Once we receive clearance from North Carolina to enter the state with Oliver, we&rsquo;ll be able to go home!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 6, 2013]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/06/july-6-2013/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/06/july-6-2013</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, we mostly hung out in the hotel room with Jan and Morgan, cuddling and spending time with Oliver. During tummy time today with Aunt Morgan, Oliver managed to turn his head from one side to the other. We were all very impressed!</p>

<p>Around mid-day, Rebecca and I both headed to the nearby pedestrian mall for some much-needed haircuts, and Jan and Morgan babysat Oliver. It was strange to be away from our baby, but good to know that Jan and Morgan were watching over him.</p>

<p>We all took a short outing to Buy Buy Baby in the afternoon. We picked up a few newborn sleeper outfits, and replaced our plastic bottles with glass bottles instead. Rebecca and I had both accidentally left nearly half of a feeding in the plastic bottles we had (which are opaque, making it hard to determine when Oliver had finished his milk). We didn&rsquo;t want to do that again.</p>

<p>That night, we went out to dinner again. Melissa tried the Moby wrap &mdash; which Rebecca had really liked &mdash; and it didn&rsquo;t work as well for her. So she put Oliver in the Ergo Baby Carrier (with the infant insert) instead. It worked much better for her, and we had another successful dinner out at a nice restaurant in the nearby pedestrian mall. Oliver peacefully slept the entire time.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 5, 2013]]></title>
    <link href="http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/05/july-5-2013/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://oliverdamien.com/blog/2013/07/05/july-5-2013</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, Oliver had his two-day check-up back at the hospital. This was supposed to be at the pediatrician&rsquo;s office, but our pediatrician is back in North Carolina, so the doctor at the hospital said we could come back to the hospital for the check-up (even though they&rsquo;re not really set up for that sort of thing). We had to wait a while, but they took good care of us. Oliver only lost a little bit of weight, as expected; otherwise, he was doing great.</p>

<p>Rebecca was clearly more tired than she realized, because she had several driving mishaps on the way to and from the hospital. Once she nearly ran a red light, and twice she nearly changed lanes when there was a car or motorcycle in the way. One of the more stressful parts of the Denver trip for her was doing all the driving in a new city.</p>

<p>At dinner time, we ventured out of the hotel with Jan and Morgan and Oliver. Rebecca wore Oliver on her chest in the Moby wrap. We had intended to get some food and bring it back to the hotel room, but Oliver was fast asleep, so we ended up deciding to eat at the restaurant, with Oliver still in the Moby wrap.</p>

<p>The night before, we&rsquo;d brought Oliver into the bed with us for part of the night, and it was really nice to have him so close. It felt somehow very wrong to put our newborn baby on the floor, several feet away from us, when recently he had literally been inside his birth mom. We did some research on cosleeping, and decided we&rsquo;d try having him sleep in the bed with us for the whole night. It was so much better on so many levels &mdash; especially the part where we got to wake up next to a beautiful sleeping baby!</p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9230007197/" title="IMG_4843 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3789/9230007197_e9214e6cfc.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_4843"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9230005973/" title="IMG_4834 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7378/9230005973_4c3bac15d7.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_4834"></a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/rdmey/9230004027/" title="IMG_4815 by rdmey, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7296/9230004027_6cc453d8d1.jpg" width="500" height="333" alt="IMG_4815"></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
